是在那之后，我被征召以后
After that, when I was drafted.
啊哈！盖世太保啊
Aha! Gestapo.
不不，是党卫军
No, no. S.S.
闭上你的嘴，白痴
Halten Sie doch den Mund, Idiot.
哦，中尉先生
Well, Herr Oberleutnant...
我还能为您做什么吗？
is there anything else I can do for you?
不了，谢谢，我已采访完毕
No, thank you. I have all the facts.
国际知名的
Union between two...
哈泽汀家族和
internationally prominent families
冯·德罗斯特·斯卡滕博格家族的结合
the Hazeltines and the von Droste
年度社交盛事
The social event of the year.
内容将在今天下午的报纸登出
It will be in the afternoon paper.
最好是这样
It had better be.
- 再见  - 祝您成功
- Auf Wiedersehen.  - Sieg heil.
至于你，施莱默
As for you, Schlemmer...
[SS既是党卫军亦是减薪的缩写]你又做回SS了…减薪
you're back in the S.S. Smaller salary.
先生，我要解释一下
Sir, let me explain.
我只是军官食堂的糕点师
I was only a pastry cook in the officers' mess.